{
    "subject": "resource/Ferret_Music",
    "predicate": "ontology/distributingLabel",
    "object": "resource/Fontana_Distribution",
    "human_readable": "Ferret Music is distributed under Fontana Distribution.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9876061081886292,
            "question": "Is Ferret Music distributed by Fontana Distribution?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8986508250236511,
            "question": "Under which distribution label is Ferret Music released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8331295251846313,
            "question": "Name the distributor of Ferret Music."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8251318335533142,
            "question": "Fontana Distribution distributes what type of music?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8227705359458923,
            "question": "Who is responsible for distributing Ferret Music?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7943540811538696,
            "question": "Which company handles the distribution of music by Ferret Music?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7936976552009583,
            "question": "What company distributes music from Ferret Music?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7917182445526123,
            "question": "What distribution company handles the distribution of Ferret Music?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7620193362236023,
            "question": "To whom does Ferret Music's distribution belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7162545323371887,
            "question": "What is the name of the distribution company for Ferret Music?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Ferret Music is distributed under Fontana Distribution.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6956_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=To whom does Ferret Music's distribution belong?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6956_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What distribution company handles the distribution of Ferret Music?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6956_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What company distributes music from Ferret Music?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6956_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6956_100.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6956_104.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6956_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6956_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6956_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6956_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6956_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6956_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6956_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6956_69.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here's the response in JSON format:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThe documents mention that Warner Music Group's Alternative Distribution Alliance acquired a stake in Ferret Music in August, 2006, and as a result, Ferret Music is currently distributed by Fontana Distribution, Alternative Distribution Alliance, and eOne Music. This implies that Ferret Music is indeed distributed under Fontana Distribution."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents state that \"Warner Music Group's Alternative Distribution Alliance acquired a stake in Ferret Music in August, 2006, and as a result is currently distributed by Fontana Distribution, Alternative Distribution Alliance and eOne Music.\" This confirms that Ferret Music is indeed distributed under Fontana Distribution."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}